JESSICA CLAIRE

resumesample@example

(555) 432-1000,

Montgomery Street, San Francisco, CA 94105

•

8

1:

A

•

(F)

SUMMARY

Detail-oriented Human Resource Benefits Specialist with 19 years in benefits coordination. Advocates positive relationships between employees, employers and insurance companies. Knowledge and experience of Microsoft Suite, Google, and Department of Public Instruction's websites as required in educational environment. Ability to expand knowledge of duties within the job description by attending additional educational seminars and continued education classes. Ability to organize and prioritize work schedule according to case load. Ability to delegate and supervise work to other employees when required help is needed. Ability to be flexible and work under pressure with a time frame deadline within the job description. Ability to work unsupervised and make decisions to the best of my knowledge in a professional manner. Ability to relate to outside personnel and represent the organization in a positive and professional manner.

HIGHLIGHTS

- · Benefits administrator
- Employment law knowledge
- Employee relations
- Manager coaching and supe
- Meeting and event manage
- Employee policies/handboo development
- Performance management strategies and evaluations
- Interviewing/exit interview

EDUCATION

Northeast Wisconsin Technica College

Green Bay, WI · May 2004 â€

Associates Degree: Superviso Management - GPA: Supervisory Management

University of Oshkosh Oshkosh, WI • Jan 2008 – –

Bachelor's Degree: Liberal Science - GPA: Magna Cum Laude Liberal Science Magna Cum Laude Graduate certificate in Organizational Administration Program

EXPERIENCE

Transdevna - HR/Office Manager Detroit, MI, • • 1995 - 2014

- Conducted benefits administration for 150 benefit-eligible employees.
- Designed the employee performance evaluation process and merit program.
- Addressed inquires from employees and management regarding new-hire activity and ongoing employee relation issues.
- Created and implemented the exit and interview program process.
- Advised top management on appropriate employee corrective actions.
- Created and modified job descriptions within all departments.
- Worked with senior-level management to create fair and consistent HR policies and procedures.
- Develop school district contracts (approximately 55 school districts) and individual contracts for professional teaching staff (approximately 150 contracts) on a yearly basis.
- Processed all salary changes stemming from merit increases, promotions, bonuses and pay adjustments.
- Created and managed more than 150 confidential personnel records.team
- Worked with leadership committees, supervise and manage office personnel and professional staff, and coordinate agency activities/needs as assigned.
- Created and managed more than 150 confidential personnel records.
- Supported all employees at all levels, including executive leadership.
- Maintained and coordinated the agency auto fleet, including bids on new/used autos and the resale of autos when the auto fleet needed to be updated.

Loma Linda University Medical Center - Bartender and Cocktail Waitress - Parttime

Redlands, CA, • • 1991 - 1995

- · Bartending and cocktail waitress duties included bartending, planning and organizing fundraisers, weddings, and other social events.
- Coordinated and worked directly with customer on one-to-one basis.

Cooperative Educational Service Agency 8 - Staff Development Assistant City, STATE, • • 1982 - 1995

- \bullet $\,$ Created and distributed inservice, workshop, and university promotional flyers to approximately 55 school districts, both public and private.
- Organized yearly calendar of activities for all departments in the organization (approximately 12 departments).
- Organized and coordinated all activities involved with in-services and workshops, which included pre and post activities, in-house and within the school district requesting the service.
- Coordinated telephone and written communications in regards to all inservice and workshop activities
- Supervised and evaluated several part-time assistants of the program, including Green Thumb assistants

Cooperative Educational Service Agency 8 - Media/Librarian Assistant City, STATE, • • 1977 - 1982

- Cataloged library materials (multi-media materials, books, etc.)
- Distributed library materials to 26 school districts in regular and special education
- General secretarial work, including distributing and correcting test for special education classes.

SKILLS

 $administrative, \ assembly, \ agency, \ Brochures, \ Communication \ Skills, \ contracts, \ human$ resource, HR, Image, insurance, lathe, team leadership, machinery, Management Skills, materials, Access, Excel, Microsoft Suite, office, PowerPoint, Word, Newsletters, organizing, paint, Personnel, Record keeping, secretarial, teaching, Telephone, welder, Workshops, written communications, Writing Skills

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION